<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on BarkBlog</title>
    <link>http://dogblog.pages.dev/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on BarkBlog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://dogblog.pages.dev/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWGG - Breaking Out</title>
      <link>http://dogblog.pages.dev/posts/a-wolf-gals-guide-breaking-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogblog.pages.dev/posts/a-wolf-gals-guide-breaking-out/</guid>
      <description>AWGG - Breaking Out Of Jail&#xA;So, you end up in a shell, and you realize you&amp;rsquo;re stuck in jail. What do you do now? You break out of course!&#xA;Step 1: Enumeration&#xA;The first thing you&amp;rsquo;ll want to do is basic enumeration. Start finding what binaries you have access to while &amp;ldquo;locked up&amp;rdquo;. At the very LEAST you&amp;rsquo;ll have access to shell one-liners, but any compilers, interpreters, or packages for other languages (gcc, python, lua, node, etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWGG - RF Hacking Recommendations</title>
      <link>http://dogblog.pages.dev/posts/a-wolf-gals-guide-rf-hacking-recommendations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogblog.pages.dev/posts/a-wolf-gals-guide-rf-hacking-recommendations/</guid>
      <description>A Wolf Gal&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Getting Started&amp;rdquo; Guide to RF Hacking for Dummies:&#xA;More and more people are wondering where I get my kit from, especially people wanting to break into infosec, so I&amp;rsquo;m putting this together to hopefully give some basic recommendations for intro wireless pentesting equipment. This is NOT a comprehensive list, nor is it the be-all-end-all of equipment either, but rather some tools I&amp;rsquo;ve used in my day-to-day doing wireless audits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intro</title>
      <link>http://dogblog.pages.dev/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogblog.pages.dev/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Hello!&#xA;My name is Rey, and this blog is about my life experiences in tech. Many posts will be technical rambling, information security related issues, and deep dives into projects im working on, while others may be about the furry fandom, queer discovery, and my transition.&#xA;Here are a few of my socials that I&amp;rsquo;m most active on if you want to keep up with me!&#xA;BlueSky Mastodon Telegram A few interesting things about me!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
